digitalsynopsis.com 2018-12-26

# Digital Synopsis - Privacy Policy

At DigitalSynopsis.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by DigitalSynopsis.com and how it is used.

## Log files

Like many other Web sites, DigitalSynopsis.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and web beacons

DigitalSynopsis.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## DoubleClick DART cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on DigitalSynopsis.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to DigitalSynopsis.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

  * Google Adsense
  * Media.net

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on DigitalSynopsis.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

DigitalSynopsis.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. DigitalSynopsis.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

## Content policy

**Owners:  **All images, photographs, advertisements, logos, brand slogans, artwork, animations, infographics, slideshows and case studies published on DigitalSynopsis.com are copyright and intellectual property of their respective owners. Every care is taken to credit and provide a source link back to the original creator(s) of work. If there is an article where the attribution information is missing or incorrect, or if you wish to have your work taken off this website, contact us at info@digitalsynopsis.com. You can also use our social media channels (mentioned above) to get in touch with us.

**Visitors:**  You may view, download for caching purposes only, and print pages or images from the website for your own personal use, subject to the restrictions set out below and elsewhere in these terms and conditions.

**You must not:**

  1. Republish material from this website (including republication on another website);
  2. Sell, rent or sub-license material from the website;
  3. Show any material from the website in public;
  4. Reproduce, duplicate, copy or otherwise exploit material on our website for a commercial purpose;
  5. Edit or otherwise modify any material on the website;
  6. Edit or otherwise modify any material printed off or downloaded in any way;
  7. Use any illustrations, photographs, video or audio sequences or graphics separately from any accompanying text; or
  8. Redistribute material from this website except for content specifically and expressly made available for redistribution.

Where content is specifically made available for redistribution, it may only be redistributed within your organisation after securing permission from the original content owner/creator. Our status (and that of any identified contributors) as the authors of material on our site must always be acknowledged.

## Affiliate disclaimer

Digital Synopsis is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.

This website contains endorsements for products and services, which means when you click on a link that we recommend, we may receive a commission. Not every link is an affiliate link, but some are.

For all queries, suggestions and feedback, contact us at [info@digitalsynopsis.com](mailto:info@digitalsynopsis.com "Open mail")
